Gabrielle Wiggins

Developer

Accomplished Developer with 2.5 years of experience seeking a position with an aggressive organization versed in the production of high-quality solutions. I bring a comprehensive understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build client-facing forms and landing pages.

Experience

2015-03 - Codes/Content Specialist

Current

Tyler Technologies, Inc. -Remote

- Manage web development projects using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript from designs improving multi-platform compatibility
- Work closely with programmers and clients to deliver requested functionality
- o QA testing and bug tracking in TestRail and JIRA
- Supervise and manage workflow of other Code Administrators
- Manage and send client announcements and communications via ZOHO
- o Develop analytical reports utilizing Excel
- o Data cleaning and verification
- o Produce automatic data and royalty reports utilizing Python
- Sales support activities
- Lead product webinar sessions

2012-05 - Clerical Scheduler

2015-03

Northside Hospital -Atlanta, GA

- Lead patients through the Radiology check-in process and ensure care
- o Educate patients, employees, and doctors on Radiology processes
- Schedule patients
- o Managed insurance and billing process utilizing computer systems

Education

2015-01 Georgia State University

B.S. Economics

Personal Info

Phone

404-432-2250

Location

Fernandina Beach, FL

E-mail

gabr26@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/gabwiggins

Skills

HTML, CSS

JavaScript

VS Code

QA Testing via JIRA

Microsoft Access

Python

ReactJS

Teamwork

High Attention to Detail

Communication

Problem-solving